Hello.
We're going to be speaking about cross stitch craft kits today.
My name is Daniel King, and I'm an experienced pattern maker, designer and sewer.
Cross stitch craft kits are kits that you can order through many craft stores or art supply stores.
These kits allow you to do different designs.
What the kit incorporates is a fabric background, usually the different colored threads, and a hoop for hooping and taut, to make the fabric taut.
With these designs you can make, typically, any type of plaque, maybe stockings for Christmas, or even portraits.
It allows you to take these different threads and stitch one through the fabric and to follow along the design to create whatever design it is.
These kits are available in most craft stores, and it gives you some flexibility as to what kind of designs you like.
Again, we're talking about cross stitch....cross stitch craft kits.
My name is Daniel King.
Thank you.